Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Subject files, 1959-1976; 96 linear feet
  - 1969
    - Foreign Relations
      - Africa
        - Rhodesia (Box 179)
      - Alliance for Progress (Box 179)
      - Asia
        - Thailand (Box 179)
        - Vietnam
          - General, 3 folders (Box 179)
          - General, 2 folders (Box 180)
          - Constitutionality (Box 180)
          - Disengagement, 2 folders (Box 180)
          - Lederer Article (Box 180)
          - Mylai Incident (Box 180)
          - Peace Talks, 2 folders (Box 180)
          - P.O.W. (Box 180)
          - Referendum (Box 180)
      - China (Box 180)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 180)
      - Korea, Pueblo (Box 180)
      - Latin America
        - Bolivia (Box 180)
        - Honduras (Box 180)
      - Middle East
        - Arab-Israel, 2 folders (Box 180)
      - South Africa (Box 180)
    - Health
      - Air Pollution, 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Cigarettes, 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Detroit Public Health Service (Box 180)
      - Finch, Secretary Robert (Box 180)
      - Mental Health (Box 180)
      - NARCO (Drug Abuse Center) (Box 180)
      - Narcotics (Box 180)
      - Water Fluoridation (Box 180)
    - Highways
      - Beautification (Box 181)
      - Bridges (Box 181)
      - Bridges, Sault Ste. Marie (toll) (Box 181)
      - Michigan
        - General (Box 181)
        - Access Roads (Box 181)
        - M99 (Box 181)
        - Proposed Routes (Box 181)
      - Traffic Safety (Box 181)
    - House of Representatives
      - Adam Clayton Powell (Box 181)
      - Rivers, Mendel (Box 181)
    - Housing
      - General
        - 701 Planning (Box 181)
        - Lumber Prices (Box 181)
        - Mobile Homes (Box 181)
        - Public Housing (Box 181)
        - Urban Development (Box 181)
        - Urban Renewal (Box 181)
    - Immigration, Alien Registration (Box 181)
    - Indians
      - 1969, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - Treaty of Saginaw (Box 181)
    - Inventions
      - Copyrights (Box 181)
      - Patents (Box 181)
      - Patents, Porter, Phil (Box 181)
    - Labor
      - Construction Cutbacks (Box 181)
      - Discrimination (Box 181)
      - Domestics (Box 181)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity, Textile Industry (Box 181)
      - Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 181)
      - Manpower Training, Migrants (Box 181)
      - Migrant Workers (Box 181)
      - National Labor Relations Board (N.L.R.B.) (Box 181)
      - Strikes (Box 181)
      - Strikes, Calumet and Hecla Mining Co. (Box 181)
      - Strikes, Oil Strike (Box 181)
      - Strikes, Teachers (Box 181)
      - Wages, Prices (Box 181)
      - Workmen's Compensation (Box 181)
    - Natural Resources
      - Beaches (Box 181)
      - Conservation
        - 1969, 2 folders (Box 181)
        - Endangered Species (Box 181)
        - Environmental, Teach-in U of M (Box 181)
        - Fish and Wildlife (Box 182)
        - Oil Drilling in Lake Erie (Box 182)
        - Pictured Rocks, 2 folders (Box 182)
        - Sylvania Tract (Box 182)
      - Federal Water Pollution Commission (Box 182)
      - Lake Levels (Box 182)
      - Lake Restoration, Messenger -- Hodunk Chain of Lakes (Box 182)
      - Michigan Dept. of Natural Resources (Box 182)
      - National Forest, Ottawa, Sylvania Tract (Box 182)
      - Saline Water (Box 182)
      - Water Levels (Box 182)
      - Water Pollution
        - General, 3 folders (Box 182)
        - Holding Tanks for Boats (Box 182)
        - Int'l Joint Commission (Box 182)
        - Kalamazoo River (Box 182)
        - Waste Treatment (Box 182)
    - Peace Corps, 1969 (Box 182)
    - Post Office
      - Objectionable Mail -- Pornographic, 3 folders (Box 182)
      - Post Master, Winton M. Blount (Box 182)
    - Power
      - Edison Sault Electric Co. (Box 183)
      - Nuclear Plants (Box 183)
    - President
      - Criticism (Box 183)
      - Criticism-Appt., Yost and Kissinger (Box 183)
      - Executive Reorganization (Box 183)
      - Federal Appointments (Box 183)
      - Federal Appointments, (Otepka) (Box 183)
      - Nixon Cabinet (Box 183)
      - Oath of Office (Box 183)
      - Power (Box 183)
      - Vatican Ambassador (Box 183)
      - Vice President Agnew (Box 183)
    - Recreation
      - Everglades (Box 183)
      - Ice Rink, Calumet-Laurium, Keweenaw Community (Box 183)
      - Michigan (Box 183)
      - Michigan-Stone Lake (Box 183)
    - Science
      - NASA
        - General (Box 183)
        - Back-Contamination (Box 183)
        - Criticism Spending (Box 183)
      - Nuclear Tests (Box 183)
      - Research
        - General (Box 183)
        - Germ Warfare, "First Tuesday TV Show" (Box 183)
        - Laboratory Animals (Box 183)
        - Medical (Box 183)
    - Security, Internal
      - Communism (Box 183)
      - HUAC (House Un-American Activities Committee) (Box 183)
      - John Birch Society (Box 183)
      - SACB (Box 183)
      - Security Risks (Box 183)
      - Sedition Statutes (Box 183)
    - Senate
      - Age Limit (Box 183)
      - Committees (Box 183)
      - Congressional, Medal of Honor (Box 183)
      - Criticism (Box 183)
      - Criticism, Kennedy, Senator (Box 183)
      - Dodd, Senator (Box 183)
      - Duties (Box 183)
      - Ethics (Box 183)
      - Information (Box 183)
      - Kennedy, Edward (Box 183)
      - Kennedy, R.F. (Box 183)
      - Legislative Program (Box 183)
      - Legislative, Reorganization Act (Box 183)
      - Rule XXII (Box 183)
    - Supreme Court
      - Appointments
        - General (Box 183)
        - Haynesworth, Judge (Box 183)
        - Roth, Judge Stephen J. (Box 183)
      - Criticism (Box 183)
      - Fortas, Justice (Box 183)
      - Fortas, not answered (Box 183)
      - Impeachment (Box 183)
    - Taxes, Capital Gains (Box 183)
    - Taxes
      - Deductions (Box 184)
      - Exemptions (Box 184)
      - Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 184)
      - Income (Box 184)
      - Investment Tax Credit (Box 184)
      - Reform (Box 184)
    - Treaties
      - Geneva Treaty (Box 184)
      - Human Rights Convention (Box 184)
      - Mexican Broadcast (Box 184)
      - Non-Proliferation, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - SEATO, Southeast Asia Treaty Organization (Box 184)
    - United Nations, General (Box 184)
    - Welfare, Social
      - General (Box 184)
      - ADC, Aid to Dependent Children (Box 184)
      - Elderly (Box 184)
      - Food Budget, Lenten Observance (Box 184)
      - Food Nutrition (Box 184)
      - Medicare, Chiropractors (Box 184)
      - Moral Welfare (Box 184)
      - Population Control (Box 184)
      - Population Control Abortion (Box 184)
      - Social Welfare Program (Box 184)
  - 1970
    - Agriculture
      - Farm Programs (Box 185)
      - Insect and Pest Control (Box 185)
      - Michigan Fruit and Vegetable Industry (Box 185)
      - Migrant Housing (Box 185)
      - Subsidies (Box 185)
      - Tobacco (Box 185)
    - Appropriations
      - General (Box 185)
      - Agriculture (Box 185)
      - Ann Arbor Fisheries, 2 folders (Box 185)
      - HEW
        - General (Box 185)
        - Material, Health and Education, 1966 (Box 185)
        - Education (Box 185)
      - HUD (Box 185)
      - Military Appropriations (Box 185)
      - Veterans Administration (Box 185)
      - White House (Box 185)
    - Atomic Energy, General (Box 185)
    - Civil Rights
      - Black Panthers (Box 185)
      - Chicago Seven (Box 185)
      - Civil Disorders (Box 185)
      - Discrimination and Segregation (Box 185)
      - Dissent, 2 folders (Box 185)
      - Dissent (Prof. Toole) (Box 185)
      - Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 185)
      - Fair Housing (Box 185)
      - Flag (Box 185)
      - Freedom of Press (Box 186)
      - Freedom of Speech (Box 186)
      - Human Rights (Box 186)
      - Invasion of Privacy (Box 186)
      - Religion (Box 186)
      - Voting Rights, 2 folders (Box 186)
      - Women's Rights (Box 186)
    - Commerce
      - Communications, TV
        - General (Box 186)
        - CATV (Box 186)
        - Sesame Street (Box 186)
      - EDA (Box 186)
    - Congress
      - Consumers, Subcommittee for (Vice-Chairman) (Box 186)
      - Criticism (Box 186)
      - Duties (Box 186)
      - Ethics of Members (Box 186)
      - Financial Disclosure (Box 186)
      - GAO, General Accounting Office (Box 186)
      - Liberty Amendment (Box 186)
      - Nutrition and Human Needs, Senate Select Committee on, 3 folders (Box 186)
      - Obscenity and pornography, Commission on (Box 186)
      - Oceanography, Subcommittee on (Box 186)
      - Organization and Reorganization (Box 186)
      - Seniority (Box 186)
      - Small Business, Senate Select Committee on (Box 186)
      - Student Unrest, Commission on (Box 186)
    - Crime
      - Act of, 1968 (Box 186)
      - Bail Reform (Box 186)
      - Criminal Procedure (Box 186)
      - Criminal Procedure, Preventative Detention (Box 186)
      - Fifth Amendment (Box 186)
      - Gun Control, 3 folders (Box 186)
      - Gun Registration (Box 186)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 186)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 186)
      - Organized Crime (Box 186)
      - Police Training (Box 186)
      - Prevention (Box 186)
    - Defense Affairs
      - ABM, 2 folders (Box 186)
      - Army (Box 186)
      - Chemical and Biological Warfare (Box 186)
      - Troop Withdrawals (Box 186)
      - Weapons (Box 186)
    - Economics
      - Industry (Box 187)
      - Industry, Michigan Industry (Box 187)
      - Inflation, 2 folders (Box 187)
      - Minority Business Assistance (Box 187)
      - National Economy (Box 187)
      - National Priorities (Box 187)
    - Education
      - Federally Impacted Areas (Box 187)
      - University of Michigan (Box 187)
    - Elections
      - Campaign Costs (Box 187)
      - Electoral College (Box 187)
      - National Parties (Box 187)
      - National Primaries (Box 187)
      - No Election in '72 (Box 187)
      - Popular Vote (Box 187)
      - Reform (Box 187)
      - Student Involvement (Box 187)
      - Voting Age (Box 187)
      - Voting Practice (Box 187)
    - Executive Branch
      - CIA, Central Intelligence Agency (Box 187)
      - FBI, Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 187)
      - Interior, Dept. of (Box 187)
      - IRS Data Processing in Detroit (Box 187)
      - President, The (Box 187)
      - Vice-President, The (Box 187)
      - SACB, Subversive Activities Control Board (Box 187)
      - US Comm. Civil Rights (Box 187)
    - Finance
      - Banks and Banking (Box 187)
      - Spending (Box 187)
    - Foreign Relations
      - Africa (Box 187)
      - Biafra (Box 187)
      - Brazil (Box 187)
      - Cambodia, January 1970 (Box 187)
      - Cambodia, May 1970 (Box 187)
      - Cambodia, June 1970 (Box 187)
      - Cambodia, June-July 1970 (Box 187)
      - Cuba (Box 187)
      - Foreign Policy (Box 187)
      - Genocide Convention (Box 187)
      - Indochina (Box 187)
      - Ireland (Box 187)
      - Israel (Box 188)
      - Middle East (Box 188)
      - Southeast Asia (Box 188)
      - Southeast Asia (End the War) (Box 188)
      - Southern Rhodesia (Box 188)
      - United Nations (Box 188)
      - USSR (Box 188)
      - USSR, "B" Letter sent to all (Box 188)
      - VN
        - General, 3 folders (Box 188)
        - Business Executives for Peace (Box 188)
        - Draft, Senator's Report of his visit, 1967 (Box 188)
        - "Kill Cong" (Box 188)
        - POW (Box 188)
    - Forest Resources, Timber (Box 188)
    - Health and Welfare
      - General (Box 188)
      - Cigarettes (Box 188)
      - Drugs-Medicine (Box 188)
      - Narcotics, 2 folders (Box 188)
      - OEO, Moms and Tots (Box 188)
      - Population Control (Box 188)
      - Welfare Cadillac (Box 188)
    - Highways
      - Bridges
        - Pine River (Box 188)
        - Zilwaukee (Box 188)
      - Interstate, I-696 (Box 188)
      - State (Box 188)
      - State, US-131 (property along) (Box 188)
    - Housing
      - #235 (Box 189)
      - FHA (Box 189)
      - Model Cities (Box 189)
      - Public Housing (Box 189)
      - Urban Renewal (Box 189)
    - Indian Affairs
      - Alcatraz to the Indians (Box 189)
      - Fishing (Box 189)
      - General (Box 189)
      - Health (Box 189)
      - Living Conditions (Box 189)
      - Treaties (Box 189)
      - White Earth Indians (Box 189)
    - Institutions, Penal Institutions (Box 189)
    - Judiciary
      - Impeachment (U.S. Supreme Court) (Box 189)
      - US Supreme Court (Box 189)
    - Labor
      - ILO, International Labor Organization (Box 189)
      - Migrant Housing (Box 189)
      - Migrant labor (Box 189)
      - Migrant Legal Action Program (Box 189)
      - NLRB, National Labor Relations Board (Box 189)
      - NW Orient (Box 189)
      - Philadelphia Plan (Box 189)
      - Strikes (Box 189)
      - Strikes, GM (Box 189)
      - Teamsters (Box 189)
      - Unemployment (Box 189)
      - Unions (Box 189)
      - Yablonski (Box 189)
    - Natural Resources
      - Conservation (Box 190)
      - Conservation, Isle Royale (Box 190)
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 190)
      - Sylvania Tract, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - Sylvania Tract, Conservation Meeting in Milwaukee (Box 190)
      - Water Pollution, Lake Lansing (Box 190)
    - Nominations
      - Carswell, Judge (Box 190)
      - DeMascio, Judge Robert (Box 190)
      - U.S. Circuit Court (Box 190)
      - U.S. District Court (Box 190)
      - U.S. District Court, Feikens, John (Box 190)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 190)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, Carswell (Box 190)
    - Parks and Recreation
      - Forest (Box 190)
      - Sylvania Dedication, September 22, 1967 (Box 190)
      - Sylvania Tract (Box 190)
    - Political Affairs
      - General (Box 190)
      - Campaign, 1970
        - January-February 1970 (Box 190)
        - March-April 1970 (Box 190)
        - May-June 1970 (Box 190)
        - July-August 1970 (Box 190)
        - September-October 1970 (Box 190)
        - November-December 1970 (Box 190)
        - Other Candidates (Box 191)
        - Lenore Romney (Box 191)
      - Committees (Box 191)
      - Contributions (Box 191)
      - Democratic Party (Box 191)
      - Endorsements (Box 191)
      - Issues (Box 191)
      - Student Lobby (Box 191)
    - Pollution
      - Air Pollution, 3 folders (Box 191)
      - Earth Day (Box 191)
      - Environmental Health (Box 191)
      - Environmental Teach In (Box 191)
      - Lake Michigan (Box 191)
      - St. Clair River (Box 191)
      - Sewage Disposal (Box 191)
      - Solid Waste (Box 191)
      - Water Pollution
        - January-February 1970 (Box 191)
        - March 1970 (Box 191)
        - April-May 1970 (Box 191)
        - June-August 1970 (Box 191)
        - September-November 1970 (Box 191)
        - Detergents, phosphates (Box 191)
        - Mercury (Box 191)
        - Oil (Box 191)
    - Power
      - Consumers Power Company (Box 192)
      - Edison Sault Ste. Marie (Box 192)
      - Nuclear Power (Box 192)
      - Presque Isle Electric (Box 192)
      - Upper Peninsula Power Company, 2 folders (Box 192)
    - Research
      - General (Box 192)
      - Mackinac Island (Nat'l Environment Research Center) (Box 192)
    - Security, National
      - Black Manifesto (Box 192)
      - Civil Defense (Box 192)
      - Communism (Box 192)
      - Detention Camps (Box 192)
      - Extremist Groups (Box 192)
      - SACB (Box 192)
      - Un-American Activities (Box 192)
    - Selective Service
      - Alternate Service (Box 192)
      - Conscientious Objectors (Box 192)
      - Deferments (Box 192)
      - Draft (Box 192)
      - Lottery (Box 192)
      - Reform (Box 192)
      - Volunteer Army (Box 192)
    - Servicemen and Veterans, Pay Allowance (Box 192)
    - Space
      - Financing (Box 192)
      - Lunar Material (Box 192)
      - NASA (Box 192)
    - State Government
      - Attorney General (Box 192)
      - Civil Rights Commission (Box 192)
      - Snowmobiles, Licensing (Box 192)
    - Taxes
      - Federal (Box 192)
      - Income (Box 192)
      - Payment (Box 192)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 192)
      - State (Box 192)
    - Trade
      - Airports and Airways (Box 193)
      - Exports (Box 193)
      - Foreign Investment (Box 193)
      - Imports (Box 193)
      - International (Box 193)
      - Merchant Marine (Box 193)
      - Ports, Harbors, Shipyards, Docks (Box 193)
      - Supersonic Transport (Box 193)
      - Rail (Box 193)
      - Tariffs (Box 193)
      - Transportation, Air (Box 193)
      - Water, Great Lakes Commission Compact, 2 folders (Box 193)
  - 1971
    - Agriculture
      - Commodities
        - Cherries (Box 193)
        - Strawberries (Box 193)
      - Industries (Box 193)
      - Soil Survey and Soil Conservation, 3 folders (Box 193)
    - Appropriations
      - Dept. of Agriculture (Box 193)
      - Health Professions (Box 193)
      - HEW
        - General (Box 193)
        - Education
          - March-May 1971 (Box 193)
          - June 1971 (Box 193)
          - June-December 1971 (Box 193)
      - Military spending (Box 194)
      - Nursing Programs (Box 194)
      - Social Work Education (Box 194)
    - Atomic Energy
      - General (Box 194)
      - Amchitka Island (Box 194)
    - Civil Rights
      - April 24, 1971 (Box 194)
      - Civil Disorders (Box 194)
      - Civil Rights Authorization, 1970-1971 (Box 194)
      - Community Mobilization (Box 194)
      - Detroit Coalition to End War Now (Box 194)
      - Discrimination and Segregation (Box 194)
      - Dissent (Box 194)
      - Dissent, Berrigan Brothers (Box 194)
      - Equal Opportunities (Box 194)
      - Florida, University of (Box 194)
      - Freedom of Press (Box 194)
      - Freedom of Religion (Box 194)
      - Freedom of Speech (Box 194)
      - Human Rights (Box 194)
      - Integration (Box 194)
      - Invasion of Privacy (Box 194)
      - TV, Control (Box 194)
      - Voting Rights (Box 194)
      - Women's Rights (Box 194)
      - Women's Rights, (In the Military Service) (Box 194)
    - Civil Service
      - Tank Automotive Command (Box 194)
      - U.S. Army Tank Automotive Command (Box 194)
    - Communications
      - PB, Public Broadcasting (Box 194)
      - SBA, All Pro Enterprises (Box 194)
      - TV (Box 194)
      - TV, CATV (Box 194)
    - Congress
      - Antitrust and Monopoly (Box 194)
      - Constitutional Rights, Subcommittee on (Box 194)
      - Consumer Subcommittee (Box 194)
      - Criticism (Box 194)
      - Democratic Caucus (Box 194)
      - Duties (Box 194)
      - Energy, Natural resources, and the Environment, Subcommittee on (Box 194)
      - Motion Pictures (Box 194)
      - Nutrition and Human Needs, Committee on (Box 194)
      - Members of Congress for Peace through Law (Box 194)
      - Seniority (Box 194)
      - Voting Record (Box 194)
    - Crime
      - Abolition Death Penalty (Box 194)
      - Bail Reform (Box 194)
      - Criminal Procedure (Box 194)
      - Death Penalty (Box 194)
      - Death Penalty, Stay of Execution (Box 195)
      - Gun Control (Box 195)
      - JFK Assassination (Box 195)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 195)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 195)
      - Parole (Box 195)
    - Defense Affairs
      - ABM (Box 195)
      - Lt. Calley (Box 195)
      - Kincheloe Airport (Box 195)
      - Policies (Box 195)
      - Selfridge Airport Base (Box 195)
      - Troop Withdrawal (Box 195)
    - Economy
      - Kelso Plan (Box 195)
      - Michigan Industry (Box 195)
      - National Economy (Box 195)
      - National Priorities (Box 195)
      - Unions (Box 195)
      - Wages/Prices
        - Auto Prices (Box 195)
        - Correspondence
          - January-September 1971 (Box 195)
            (Escalation)
          - General Correspondence (Box 195)
          - October 1971 (Box 195)
          - Military Pay (Box 195)
    - Education
      - Busing (Box 195)
      - Busing, Integration (Box 195)
      - Financing (Box 195)
      - School Lunch (Box 195)
    - Elections
      - Campaign Costs (Box 196)
      - Electoral College (Box 196)
      - Electoral Reform (B. Wides ), 1970-1971 (Box 196)
      - Voting Practices (Box 196)
    - Executive Branch
      - Cabinet (Box 196)
      - FBI (Box 196)
      - President (Box 196)
      - Vice-President (Box 196)
      - White House Conference on Aging (Box 196)
    - Foreign Relations
      - China (Box 196)
      - Civilian Prisoner Exchange (Box 196)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 196)
      - Genocide Treaty (Box 196)
      - Ireland (Box 196)
      - Israel (Box 196)
      - Laos (Box 196)
      - Panama Canal (Box 196)
      - Refugees (Box 196)
      - Rhodesia (Box 196)
      - South Africa (Box 196)
      - USSR (Box 196)
      - Vietnam
        - General (Box 196)
        - Correspondence
          - January-March 1971 (Box 196)
          - April-May 1971 (Box 196)
        - Oil (Box 196)
        - POW (Box 196)
    - Health and Welfare
      - Child Protection (Box 196)
      - Cigarettes (Box 196)
      - Cruelty to Animals (Box 196)
      - Headstart (Box 196)
      - Measles-Vaccinations (Box 196)
      - Medicare (Box 196)
      - Narcotics (Box 196)
      - Population Control (Box 196)
    - Highways
      - Bridges (Box 197)
      - Off Highway Safety (Box 197)
      - State (Box 197)
    - Housing and Urban Development
      - FHA
        - Detroit Area (Box 197)
        - FCH-Foundation for Cooperative Housing (Box 197)
        - Flint (Box 197)
      - Flint (Box 197)
      - Model Cities (Box 197)
      - Public Housing (Box 197)
      - Storm Sewer Projects (Box 197)
      - Urban Renewal (Box 197)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, Computer Aliens (Box 197)
    - Indian Affairs
      - General (Box 197)
      - Education Programs (Box 197)
      - Fishing Rights (Box 197)
      - Indian Culture Centers (Box 197)
      - Mainstream (Box 197)
    - Institutions, Correctional (Box 197)
    - Judiciary
      - Judiciary Cases (Box 197)
      - Jury Duty (Box 197)
      - Reform (Box 197)
      - U.S. District Court (Box 197)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 197)
    - Labor
      - Air Controllers (Box 197)
      - Employment (Box 197)
      - Migrant Labor (Box 197)
      - NYC, Neighborhood Youth Corps (Box 197)
      - Strikes (Box 197)
      - Unions (Box 197)
    - Natural Resources
      - Alaska Pipeline (Box 197)
      - Conservation (Box 197)
    - Natural Resources
      - Fuels (Box 198)
      - Lake Huron Erosion (Box 198)
      - Lake Lansing (Box 198)
      - Lake Levels (Erosion) (Box 198)
      - Lamprey EEL (Box 198)
      - Minerals (Box 198)
      - Pigeon River State Forest (Box 198)
      - SBD #1 (Box 198)
      - SBD #2 (Box 198)
      - SBD, Hydrofoil Harbor (Box 198)
      - Sylvania Tract (Box 198)
    - Nominations
      - Secretary of Agriculture (Box 198)
      - DeMascio, Judge Robert E. (Box 198)
      - Rehnquist, William H. (Box 198)
      - United Nations Ambassador (Box 198)
      - U.S. Attorney (Box 198)
      - U.S. Circuit Court (Box 198)
      - U.S. District Court (Box 198)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 198)
    - Parks and Recreation
      - Isle Royale (Box 198)
      - Wilderness Areas (Box 198)
    - Political Affairs
      - General (Box 198)
      - Campaign, 1972 (Box 198)
      - Democratic Party
        - January-July 1971 (Box 198)
        - August-December 1971 (Box 198)
      - Recall (Box 198)
      - Student Lobby (Box 198)
    - Pollution
      - Air (Box 198)
      - EPA, Environmental Protection Act (Box 198)
      - Recycling (Box 198)
      - Sewage Disposal (Box 198)
      - Solid Waste (Box 198)
      - Water Pollution (Box 198)
    - Power, Nuclear Power (Box 199)
    - Research, General (Box 199)
    - Security, National
      - American Security Council (Box 199)
      - Capitol Bombing (Box 199)
      - Civil Defense (Box 199)
      - Communism (Box 199)
      - Detention Camps (Box 199)